{
    "id": "0c487b8d7a4d46b9b54cadfad6faee1d",
    "title": "Kinds Of Adjectives",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "f8b686f8e4cf4cab99bf543f5934f767",
            "title": "Kinds Of Adjectives",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Tokyo is a big city. Here big is an ………………….",
                    "description": "Adjectives of quality show the kind or quality of a person or thing.",
                    "answers": [
                        "adjective of quality",
                        "adjective of quantity",
                        "adjective of number"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ate some rice. Here some is an ……………………….",
                    "description": "Adjectives of quantity say how much of a thing is meant.",
                    "answers": [
                        "adjective of quality",
                        "adjective of quantity",
                        "adjective of number"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The foolish crow opened his mouth to sing. Here foolish is an …………………………",
                    "description": "Adjectives of quality show the kind or quality of a person or thing.",
                    "answers": [
                        "adjective of quality",
                        "adjective of quantity",
                        "adjective of number"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has little patience. Here little is an ……………………………….",
                    "description": "Adjectives of quantity say how much of a thing is meant.",
                    "answers": [
                        "adjective of quality",
                        "adjective of quantity",
                        "adjective of number"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has lost all of his wealth. Here all is an ………………………….",
                    "description": "Adjectives of quantity say how much of a thing is meant.",
                    "answers": [
                        "adjective of quality",
                        "adjective of quantity",
                        "adjective of number"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We did not receive sufficient rain this year. Here sufficient is an",
                    "description": "Adjectives of quantity say how much of a thing is meant.",
                    "answers": [
                        "adjective of quality",
                        "adjective of quantity",
                        "adjective of number"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Each hand has five fingers. Here five is an …………………………",
                    "description": "Adjectives of number show how many persons or things are meant.",
                    "answers": [
                        "adjective of quality",
                        "adjective of quantity",
                        "adjective of number"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "There are several mistakes in your composition. Here several is an ……………………….",
                    "description": "Adjectives of number show how many persons or things are meant.",
                    "answers": [
                        "adjective of quality",
                        "adjective of quantity",
                        "adjective of number"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "January is the first month of the year. Here the adjective first is an ……………………….",
                    "description": "Ordinal numbers are all adjectives of number. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "adjective of quality",
                        "adjective of quantity",
                        "adjective of number"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Our country expects every citizen to do their duty. Here every is a ……………………………",
                    "description": "Distributive adjectives refer to each one of a group.",
                    "answers": [
                        "numeral adjective",
                        "distributive adjective",
                        "demonstrative adjective"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Neither accusation is true. Here neither is a …………………………..",
                    "description": "Distributive adjectives refer to each one of a group.",
                    "answers": [
                        "numeral adjective",
                        "distributive adjective",
                        "demonstrative adjective"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Those apples are ripe. Here those is a ……………………………..",
                    "description": "Demonstrative adjectives point out which person or thing is meant.",
                    "answers": [
                        "numeral adjective",
                        "distributive adjective",
                        "demonstrative adjective"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}